yesnetwork.com 2019-06-01

# Privacy Policy

**PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY (THIS "PRIVACY POLICY") CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS WEBSITE**

**TABLE OF CONTENTS**

  * General
  * Information Automatically Collected; Cookies; Web Beacons
  * Our Security Practices
  * How You Can Review Your Personal Information
  * Choice
  * Links
  * Special Rules for Children
  * Contact Us; Privacy Administrator
  * Notification of Changes

### General

Yankees Entertainment & Sports Network, LLC, d/b/a The YES Network ("YES") in association with MLB Advanced Media, LLC ("MLBAM") produces YESNETWORK.com, the Official Website of YES (the "Website"). We are committed to safeguarding your privacy online. This Privacy Policy is applicable to this Website only. 

You can visit and enjoy our Website without disclosing any personal information about yourself. However, we offer some special services, and for these services to work properly we will need you to share with us certain personal information about yourself. The personal information we collect may include, but is not limited to, full name, street address, e-mail address, telephone number(s) (e.g., home, work, mobile and/or fax) and birth date. We may also collect other personal information that will be identified on applicable page(s) of this Website. If you submit any personal information to us, or to any third-parties acting on our behalf, you can be assured that we will not sell, lease, or share your personal information with or to anyone else, except as follows: (1) to certain third parties , but only so that they may help us provide services you've requested and/or in certain circumstances to provide you with related offers or content; (2) upon notice posted on an applicable location of our Website where we collect your personal information for an economic transaction and notify you that we will be sharing such information with a third party, where such third party is clearly identified; and (3) on occasion, we may offer a special promotion (such as a sweepstakes, contest, fantasy baseball game or subscription to goods and/or services) on this Website in conjunction with a third-party service provider, sponsor, or promotional partner, and share your information with that service provider, sponsor, or promotional partner so that it can fulfill your request for its good and services and/or to send you other special promotions it offers, but only if you give us permission to do so.

Special Offers and Promotions. With your permission, we may also send you e-communications with special offers and promotions. If you don't want to receive these, you may change your preferences by accessing the "Newsletter" section within your Website account.

### Information Automatically Collected; Cookies; Web Beacons 

We use automatic methods such as cookies (small amounts of data, which often include an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a website's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive), single-pixel GIF images ("web beacons") or similar technologies, alone or in combination with personally identifiable information you choose to provide us, to make our Website work better, to understand Website usage and trends, to deliver a more personalized experience and to improve and deliver certain content and offerings. Examples of the information we collect and analyze using such methods include, without limitation, the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; e-mail address; login name and password; operating system type, version and computer platform; purchase history, which we may aggregate with similar information from other customers; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, on, and from our Website, including date and time; cookie information; and products you viewed or searched for. We may also use software tools to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs) and methods used to browse away from the page.

We may also use cookies to enable you to use a "shopping cart" if you want to purchase goods or services while on our Website, to store your preferences associated with video streaming or other content offered from our Website, and to deliver certain content, products, programs, and/or services based on purchase and Website usage behavior that you and/or other customers have exhibited. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the user to accept or reject most cookies. Certain cookies that are set when some video products are accessed on our Website, called local shared objects or Flash cookies, may not be managed using the settings in your web browser. Information on managing, accepting and rejecting these cookies is available from Adobe on the [Adobe website](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager03.html). If you set your browser or Adobe Flash options not to accept cookies or local shared objects, you may not be able to take advantage of certain services on our Website.

We do not transfer cookies associated with our Website to any other company, nor do we authorize any other company to access those cookies for any purpose other than as set forth in this Privacy Policy. We may allow certain third parties, such as those who deliver advertisements, content or provide other services associated with our Website to set and/or access cookies, web beacons and/or similar technologies associated with certain of our pages and/or certain emails sent by us. 

_About Our Ads._ Third-party companies that manage and deliver advertisements on our Website and other websites are commonly referred to as "network advertisers." These network advertisers who place advertisements on our Website may use cookies and web beacons to collect information about your visits to our Website in order to provide advertisements and content delivered on our Website and on other websites within such network advertiser's ad network. You may elect to opt out of targeted behavioral advertising from many major third party network advertisers by [clicking here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices). If you would like to obtain more information about common industry practices of network advertisers and/or make choices about their use of your information, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp). 

_Adware and Spyware._ We do not install any spyware or adware in connection with our Website, or distribute any commercial message, or authorize any third party to distribute any commercial message, by means of spyware or adware. "Spyware" or "adware" is any software which has been downloaded to and/or installed on an Internet user's computer, without the user's actual consent, and facilitates the distribution of any commercial message to the user. If you feel you may have spyware from another company installed on your machine, there are various anti-spyware/adware software applications available on the Internet to identify if this has occurred. 

_Social Networking._ When using our Website or when using certain third party social networking services (e.g., Facebook, Twitter, Google +) (each and collectively, a "Social Network"), you may have the option to connect your Website information and activity with your Social Network information and activity. If you authorize such a connection, you permit us to share or publish information about your activity on our Services, with that Social Network and its users, and to access certain of your Social Network information, as disclosed by you at the time you consent to the connection. Information we may share with a Social Network may include, but is not limited to: technical information about your Services activity, your Services comments or the videos you watch on our Services. Information we may access about you, with your consent, from a Social Network may include, but is not limited to, your basic Social Network information, your location data, your list of contacts, friends or followers, and certain of your activities on the Social Network. If you permit a connection between a Social Network and our Website, we (and that Social Network) may be able to identify you and to associate information received pursuant to the connection with information we already have about you. We recommend that you familiarize yourself with the privacy policy and privacy control options of any Social Network with which you choose to share information or connect to our Website.

_Aggregated Demographic Information._ We may share aggregated demographic information with third parties, but this information is not linked to any personal information that can identify you or another individual person. Therefore, no personal information is disclosed in this manner.

_Business Transfers._ As time passes, YES may be sold along with its assets, or other transactions may occur in which customer information is one of the business assets transferred. In such a case, the customer information which we have gathered may be one of the business assets we transfer.

_Disclosure for Legal Purposes._ We may be required to share your personal information and non-personal information pursuant to judicial or governmental subpoenas, warrants, or orders. If we are required to do so, we will, of course, obey the law. In addition, notwithstanding any term to the contrary in this Privacy Policy, we reserve the right to use, disclose, and/or share your personal and non-personal information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of this Website's Terms of Use or as otherwise required by law.

### Our Security Practices

Your Website account preferences are password protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas, we use industry-standard SSL encryption to protect data transmissions.

### How You Can Review Your Personal Information

If you want to review or revise the personal information you provided during registration on this Website, and whether you want to receive communications from us, you can either (1) [click here to log in](https://secure.yesnetwork.com/enterworkflow.do?flowId=registration.profile), and then click on the applicable menu option on the left side of the page, or (2) contact YESNetwork.com Customer Service at [info@yesnetwork.com](mailto:info@yesnetwork.com). If you want to close your account with us and have us delete the personal information in it (except for information that we keep for record-keeping purposes), you should contact YESNetwork.com Customer Service at [info@yesnetwork.com](mailto:info@yesnetwork.com).

### Choice

Our registration and order forms contain a box for you to indicate whether or not you consent to receive special offers and promotions from us. Unless you give us your consent to use your personal information for these purposes, we and our partners will only use it to complete the transaction or provide the service or product you have requested. If you indicate that you consent to receive communications or solicitations, but you later change your mind, you can revise your preferences by accessing the "Newsletter" section within your Website account.

### Links

Our Website contains links to other websites produced by MLB Advanced Media, L.P. and to websites and/or products operated by unrelated third parties. In addition, if you click on an advertisement on our Website, you may be directed to a web page within our Website or to a third- party website or product. Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of third-party websites or products. We encourage you to be aware of this when your leave our Website and to read the privacy policies of every website and product that collects personally identifiable information from you. This Privacy Policy applies only to this Website, unless you are notified otherwise upon accessing any third party website or product, in which case the terms and conditions set forth in such notification will apply. 

### Special Rules For Children

Because of federal law, we cannot knowingly collect and retain any personal information from a child under the age of thirteen without the consent of that child's parent. The statements in this Privacy Policy generally about our collection and use of personal information also apply to our treatment of personal information from children under the age of thirteen. Some services on our Website require the submission of a credit card number along with personal information in connection with a purchase, other services on our Website (e.g., account creation) require the submission of personal information to the Website. Except in certain cases where limited contact information may be collected and not retained, these services are not available to children under the age of thirteen. If a child who YES knows to be under the age of thirteen attempts to utilize a service on this Website which is not available to children, he/she will receive a message which relays that he/she is not eligible for the service. 

### Contact Us; Privacy Administrator

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us at: [info@yesnetwork.com](mailto:info@yesnetwork.com). 

### Notification of Changes

If we make an important change to this Privacy Policy, we will post a notification and link on our homepage so that you can review the updated policy. 

**_LAST UPDATED AND EFFECTIVE DATE: December 17, 2013_**
